The End
Sanctuary!
Goddammit, I ain't got all day!
Huh?
Like I thought, there's not a trace
of mold on you, even though you fell.
I thought Chocolatous green tea was supposed
to ravage any living thing in touch.
So how the hell are
you still in one piece?
Guess I'll just have to do
it the old-fashioned way.
Beating you over and over again
until your body stops moving.
Welcome to my sanctuary!
This won't be a quick kill.
I need to put some
distance between us fast.
No time to lose.
Oh, my God.
Cameo no sa tame ni sa e?
Hang o Hear Cairo su.
GameStop.
Let's go.
That malicious mole should
be far behind by now.
What the hell's going on?
What's with all these accidents?
Help me!
An ambulance!
Over there!
Down by the stairs!
Where did all the mold go?
Chocohata!
No one's getting eaten.
That means they did it.
Well done, Ragazzi. Excellent work.
Squalo, it's me.
Have you disposed of Buchorati?
See, I've run into a few
complications on my end.
I get around to killing Giorno,
but I've taken a bit of a
hindering blow to the head.
So to err on the side of caution,
I must share something with you.
Listen closely, Seko.
Those bastards are
headed for the Coliseum.
The Bone Boys babbling bullets said so.
They're supposed to meet someone there.
Someone who boasts of having secret
knowledge on how to fake with the boss.
It should baffle no one
then that Giorno and his
friends would be so eager to
make it to this rendezvous.
Are you getting any of this?
You must uncover this
secret before anyone else.
I'm counting on you.
All that drama over a phone call.
Still, what did he learn?
Screw you, Cioccolata!
You thought I'd get all weepy over you?
Give me a break, loser!
You lost to clowns!
Aren't you supposed to
be some kind of genius?
With perfect throwing arms full of yummy
sugar cubes and a crazy fat load of cash?
On top of that, you're super strong.
At least I thought you were.
It's the only reason why I've been
bothering to listen to you this entire time.
But it turns out you're
just another weakling!
You totally ate shit out there.
Well guess what I don't want to hang
out with you anymore, so kiss my ass.
What the he's heading
straight toward the Coliseum
someone's clued him into our
goal after the secret, are you?
I think not!
Where's the other?
Zippermen, go for the kill!
How's this?
Hey,
don't you think it's funny
how the word coliseum
sounds a hell of a lot
like the word mausoleum?
What do you think, Mr.
Language Expert?
I'm sure you wouldn't mind if I sent
you there instead, now would you?
Merda.
I was wrong to assume the only
danger was the man in the helicopter.
We're still miles away from
being out of the woods.
This tunneling fiend is a
colossal threat all on his own.
If he should slip from my grasp
and get to the Colosseum first,
I'll have unleashed a monster!
You're an awful pest, you
know that, Bucciarati.
Why bother fighting back at this point?
At such a close range, I can
outrun and outmuscle you!
I'll swat you like a fly, little twerp!
You're a pretty quick
thinker now, ain't ya?
Your big brain saved you again.
Just barely, though, so don't get cocky.
Again, that body of yours is really weird.
Just what the hell is wrong with you?
You're riddled with glass, and
yet there's not a drop of blood.
Did you see what I just saw, too?
Weird.
What do you think it is?
It was somewhere on the
second level, right?
The blinky, shiny thing?
It happened earlier, too.
There was something crawling in
the shadows just now. Must be shy.
I saw it.
It was quick, but I saw it.
It was a reflection.
No doubt from a peeping
pair of binoculars.
So that's the fellow you and your stupid
friends have been so desperate to meet.
I think I saw him in a wheelchair.
One of his legs looked like a prosthetic.
He doesn't seem like
a guy who could fight.
Guess that secret's as good as mine now.
So you can suck him, you
bloodless sack of crap.
Suck on these knuckles specifically!
So now you're making fun of me.
You and your stupid zippers.
Eat shit, copycat.
I'm not sure if you've forgotten, but
you're swimming around in my territory now.
I'm gonna rip your dumbass
apart. Take this! Thank you!
Wait, he's not hiding down there.
He's trying to move about.
I'm getting some crazy vibrations.
Just where are you off to in
such a hurry, you damn coward?
Running away with my trick? Boy,
you got a whole lot of nerve trying to
mimic me like I'm some kind of idiotic joke.
Bet you think you're hot shit
with your zipper stand right now.
Well, you're not.
All you really did was
steal my moves, little rat.
That lack of creativity is about to bite
you because I am a million times better
at this than your dumbass will ever be you
won't send one foot in the Coliseum. The
walls
are turning
rubbery again so
he's already on my trail but this noise?
There's no question it's rushing straight
toward me with an incredible speed.
Sound may be able to travel
fastest through solids,
but this liquid-like material
won't offer me much protection.
Damn it!
That probably means he's been able to
hear my every move this whole time.
Well, would you look at that?
You actually got quite far for
a complete rookie, that is.
You can't hide.
I know exactly where you are.
A pathetic 20 meters ahead
and slightly to the left.
Turning right, huh?
Ten more meters to go.
Now just seven meters.
Five meters.
Strangling you now would be too lenient.
Hope you know you've just buried
yourself alive, Bucciarati.
How are you gonna dodge when
you're surrounded by dirt?
It'll be no different from punching
a helplessly tied up little worm.
Just two more meters.
A water pipe.
You're trying to shake
me with that? Idiot.
What the hell do you take me for?
You out of smart ideas?
Oh, these pathetic little stunts of
yours freaking reek of utter desperation.
You don't even have to say a single word.
Judging from your actions,
I can already tell
you've come to terms with
meeting your end at the
hands of my sanctuary.
I'm not sure exactly where,
but I can sense your carcass
languishing just 20 meters away.
Staying still in the hopes
that I won't find you, huh?
Just like a little bunny.
Or are you up to something?
Let me guess.
You got another plan?
You're a quick thinker after all.
Too bad.
All the brains in the world
can't save you from me now.
Time for you to die, Smarty Pants!
That sound just now is new.
What's he up to?
It's got me surrounded. Damn.
Even all those big rocks in the ground...
turn right into mud when they're
exposed to my Sanctuary's touch.
But the moment my body
starts moving away from them,
they harden right back into stone.
Got a little tip for you.
Listen well and you'll definitely
make it out of this alive, maybe.
The only thing you gotta do to live is
remain as still as you possibly can.
I mean, I guess it'd take a real
miracle for you to pull that off.
Like you must have heard of the
guy who was hanged three times,
but lived because the rope kept
breaking every time they dropped him.
Ain't that nuts?
Miss Zero, I can't stay
down here much longer.
But resurfacing now
isn't an option either.
I prepared myself for this.
But should they fail to make it, I'll
have no choice but to destroy the Arrow.
All hope hinges on them
crossing paths with it.
If, in his true heart of hearts, a
hero wishes to defeat Emperor Crimson,
he will have no choice but to
learn of the Arrow's power.
Fate has decided that hero
shall not be me, but them.
Twelve years ago, it entered my
possession after the battle in Egypt.
The horrors this artifact has wrought will
continue to rage on until they stop it.
It's all rather ironic,
one might venture to say.
Deemed pariahs and cast from society,
they sought family in the Mafia.
Yet here they are, determined to save the
same world from which they were shunned.
I can do little more than
hope that you, Bucciarati,
will be able to make it here alive.
All will be rendered pointless
if you fail to triumph.
When that happens, the arrow and
its secret must fade into oblivion.
So I patiently await
you, Harbinger of Hope.
It's the only thing I'm able to do.
We'll begin once you're here.
Until then, I'll continue
to preserve its true power.
Just as I have been for all those
interminable and torturous years.
It's no use. I gotta move.
There he goes.
He finally gave in.
Is that you I hear squirming
around 12 meters to the right?
Wait, you can't be thinking about
taking shelter under the Coliseum.
That's the dumbest idea you've had today?
As if I let you do that!
He's coming in hot!
I can hear him frantically
working his way closer and closer!
Such a noisy target!
I can easily tell he's just ten meters
in front of me now eight meters!
I can't possibly hope to outrun him!
Come forth!
Whoa! Not bad.
I take it back.
This was a damn cool scheme for sure.
Oh, Bucciarati,
is this really how the great mafioso
flails when he's been backed into a corner?
Well,
big congrats to you on being the first
person to successfully hide from Sanctuary,
even if it was just for a bit.
But playtime's over.
I'll get you any second now.
You can't hide forever.
Of course, you're welcome
to try if you want.
It'll just make killing
you that much sweeter.
What happened?
My skin, it's...
Even the stone pavement
is melting into mud!
And so will your body
once I finally get to it!
The closer I get, the Capri you'll become!
Isn't that just swell?
Found you! You're mine!
You really made me work for
it, but I've got you at last!
All that remains between us
is one and a half meters.
Look how close you got to
making it to the Coliseum.
Gosh darn it, you almost got there.
Well, too bad!
That tantalizing secret is all mine!
Zipperman, showtime!
Huh?
Some people might call it a miracle.
Even I'm baffled.
I could shatter any bone in my body
without feeling an ounce of pain.
My heart doesn't beat, so
I don't bleed much either.
Nothing truly hurts me anymore.
Knowing that, I laid a trap for you.
Here's hoping my eardrums are
as resilient as the rest of me.
It seems I was right to wait.
I knew you'd soon start carelessly
driving everything down into the ground.
From the street lamps, to the roadsides,
heck, even a couple of parked
cars, right down to their tires.
Silly me, I'm wasting my
time lecturing the death.
You've gone and done it now,
you rotten son of a bitch!
Well, I'm perfectly fine, see?
I can still hear yeah
yeah that horrible tire
pump came from over
there which can only mean
Where did he go? Damn it!
What the shit did that bastard do to me?
How did I mistake him for a freaking car?
Your eardrums have just been ruptured.
What did you call your
ground melting stand again?
Sanctuary, right?
Without your keen sense of hearing serving
as its sonar, it seems rather impotent.
You were trying to burst my
eardrums this entire time!
You think my sanctuary is useless
without my super-powered sonar skills?
That's stupid and not
true at all! Get away!
I'm warning you asshole!
Stay back!
Relax, I won't kill you.
However,
now that you know about the
man we're supposed to meet,
I can't exactly let you run off either.
So I'll incapacitate
you posthaste. You dick!
I know you said something about
incapacitating me just now!
I...
I'm not stupid, I can tell!
Zip it, Walnut Head.
I can barely understand you.
Come here, kid!
Go ahead, try and lay even a finger on me.
I'll turn this meat
shield into a pile of mud.
Then I'll fling his bits
at you and run for it!
I'm sure you wouldn't want to have bloody
kitty chunks on your hands, would ya?
You know what?
Change of plans!
Instead of getting rid of the boss myself,
I think I'll just report to him
everything that happened today?
so he'll call me a good boy and
give me a nice juicy reward.
Yeah, yeah, that's brilliant.
I'm better off just having the
Family take care of me forever.
Hey brat, get me a taxi.
Come on, raise those arms.
Up, hail me a cab.
I said work those damn noodle arms.
Hey, are you deaf or something, huh?
Stupid kid, hurry up.
A taxi! Hail me! A cow!
Not one step closer!
Or I swear I'm gonna do it!
I'll melt this kid down to mud!
What, are you playing dumb?
I know you can hear me, Bucciarati!
Come on now, you can drop
the big tough guy routine!
I know your stance range
is a measly two meters!
You think just because my leg's broken
that I can't put more distance between us?
Don't you dare try me!
I'll kill this sweet child!
Did you want to tickle me or something?
I'm out of range, dummy!
See?
I told you so.
All you did was graze me up!
What the hell did you just do to me?
Your zipper!
What is it doing to my...
Where did it get...
Not that I needed confirmation, but
I guess it's nice to know for sure.
There was no way Bucciarati
would have let any
sort of harm befall an
innocent kid like me.
Ah, crap!
Gotta get this thing off of me back!
Cioccolata!
I managed to locate and catch up to
Seko by tracing his cell phone signal.
It looks like things are
straying from the boss's plans.
To think that Seko had
already been beaten.
That likely means Chocolata's out too.
Also, why is Bucciarati
out here all by himself?
Isn't he usually with Giorno,
Giovanna, and Narancia?
My strength, it's gone.
I can't lift my miseria.
Even my vision's blurring.
Am I finally out of time?
I knew this moment would come.
But why now?
Just fiction What is the truth
They have the mission They are the
passion But they dare to tell us
What's bad and what's good Stand
up Join us Come on Just see this
We are the power Cause they're
the future Cause we are the
fighters Just fighting for the right
I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous,
I'm so nervous,
Thank
you.